The coins got no top cuz the dollar's
got no bottom. Most of the crypto coins
will never make an all-time high ever
again. And uh the faster people realize
that, the better. In crypto, we have
this weird dynamic where things can be
zombies. [music] They can kind of become
ghost chains or whatever. And so, you
can hold on to the dream for a long
time, but it doesn't mean the dream is
reality. The US equity market is a great
thing to study because it shows that
strength begets more strength. Returns
beget more returns. And so, when you
look at the stock market, when is the
best day to buy in [music] the stock
market any given year? At an all-time
high.
I'm back with co-host [music] Bonnie
Chang at the uh Consensus Miami, one of
the premier crypto conferences in the
world. Joining me and Bonnie right now
is Anthony Pompliano, host of The Pomp
Podcast. Welcome to the show, Anthony.
>> Absolutely. Thanks for having me.
>> Good to see you. Thank you for joining
Bonnie and I. All right, you've been
tweeting a lot about crypto recently.
Most of the crypto industry is dead and
never coming back. Eventually, people
will realize it. Tell us more.
Well, what else is there to say? I think
a lot of people are confused. They think
that uh most of the crypto coins will
never make an all-time high ever again.
And uh the faster people realize that,
the better. It doesn't mean that
everything is going to go to zero. Just
means that most of the long-tail assets
didn't find product market fit. And so,
they're basically zombies at this point.
They're just
>> One of the comments to that uh tweet was
pretty good. I was reading the thread.
And they said, "Hey, look, th- this is a
flushing out period. The good projects
are here to stay. In every cycle, you
flush out the scammers and the projects
that have no future. Maybe this is good
for the industry." Well, of course it's
good to get rid of all the things that
don't work, but I don't think that that
means that all of a sudden a bunch of
things come back. My general view is
that Bitcoin is going to survive, stable
coins will survive, equity
infrastructure will survive, and
tokenization will survive. Those four
themes are pretty much where most of the
value, if not all the value, is going to
accrue moving forward. The problem
becomes that there's still an entire
industry of people who are trying to
make altcoins, you know, and other types
of assets, something, but they're never
coming back. They're They're dead.
They're zombies. If this was not in
crypto, they would go bankrupt. They
would file for bankruptcy. They would go
out of business. That capital and that
talent would get reallocated to other
opportunities. In crypto, we have this
weird dynamic where things can be
zombies. They can kind of become ghost
chains or whatever. And so, you can hold
on to the dream for a long time, but it
doesn't mean the dream is reality. And I
think people just need to recognize
that. A few weeks ago, your video was
titled Bitcoin bull market is happening
now. Tell us more. Well, Bitcoin
bottomed at 60K. Now, we're back to
80,000. So, it's up 30% off of the
bottom. And I think that what people
don't usually give enough credit to is
the US equity market is a great thing to
study because it shows that strength
begets more strength. Returns beget more
returns. And so, when you look at the
stock market, when is the best day to
buy in the stock market any given year?
At an all-time high. If you buy at an
all-time high day, you are likely to
outperform buying any other day of the
year. Well, same thing with Bitcoin is
if you buy Bitcoin when it has strength
to it, it is starting to go higher, that
momentum carries through. And so, when I
tweeted that, we weren't at 80K. I think
we were somewhere in the high 60s,
right? Well, now we're even higher. And
I think we'll continue to go higher
through the end of the year. And do we
get back to an all-time high or not? I'm
not sure. But what I do know is that
when you have a big flush like you had
in the Bitcoin price, you had the fear
and greed index go to single digits,
which I'd never seen before. And now you
have this kind of very persistent bid in
this grind back up to 80K. It tells you
that it is likely that we are going
higher, not lower. And so, I think that
people just need to get comfortable with
the fact that Bitcoin is a very
different asset today than it was a
decade ago.
Are you worried about anything? Quantum
risk? Any risk that people talk about?
Every single risk that you could
outline, the single biggest
mitigator is the humans that are
involved in Bitcoin. The humans are
smart. We figure out how to do mining.
We figure out how to do security. We
figure out how to do transactions. We
figure out how to do all these different
things. So, every time I hear that
there's some technology risk, I just
think I will bet on Bitcoiners over that
technology any day of the week because
Bitcoiners are very smart. We were able
to create and help thrive an asset that
reached over 1.5 trillion dollar
valuation. There's no CEO, there's no
board of directors, there's no
management team, no marketing budget,
etc. And so, if we can do that,
Bitcoiners can do anything in the world
and I think that that is the ultimate
mitigater for all these different risks
is that the Bitcoiners will figure it
out.
Is there anything except Bitcoin that
you're betting on? Well, stable coins,
equity infrastructure, and tokenization,
you know. Uh people forget, but back in
2016, 2017, 2018 time frame, uh I was
very, very bullish on tokenizing all
these assets. And it wasn't that I
thought they competed with Bitcoin. I
always thought Bitcoin was kind of this,
you know, crypto native or Bitcoin
native asset that was very unique. Um it
was going to be this great store of
value. But as I've talked about for a
long time is if you go back pre-1980s,
everything was analog. You had a
physical stock certificate, a physical
bond, physical deed to your home, etc.
And then in the 80s into the 90s, we
electronified everything. And so we went
to electronic uses for all of those
different assets. Now we're just going
to digitize them. They're going to
become digital tokens. But as a user, I
don't really care what the back end
plumbing is. All I know is that I'm
buying Apple stock. I want Apple
exposure. And so that tokenization is
going to be a big theme. It's just not
going to be the way that people thought.
It's not like some brand new coin that
can't exist in the equity market. It's
just simply allowing the plumbing to get
better.
I mean tokenization is great, but where
does a value go? Are we doing
the infrastructure? Is it the equity
>> infrastructure will accrue value, but
mostly it's to Apple or to whatever the
asset is, right? You're not buying Apple
stock in a tokenized form because it's
tokenized. You're buying it because you
want Apple stock. And so ultimately the
same thing in the traditional market's
going to happen here is you're just
going to have value accrue to wherever
it is treated best.
Uh the soon-to-be new Fed chair, Kevin
Warsh, said that uh AI and Bitcoin will
be the next drivers of the American
economy. This is coming from a would-be
Fed chair.
What do you make of these remarks? How
important is it? Or what is the
significance of this coming from the
Federal Reserve? Look, we got a public
company called ProShares Financial.
That's a literally our entire thesis is
AI and Bitcoin are going to end up being
the two driving forces in finance. And
if you think about AI as offense, it's
going out, it's building products, it's
creating services, it's trying to go and
drive solutions to the problems that our
customers have. But then you then take
that revenue and that profit, you put on
your balance sheet in the form of
Bitcoin to protect it. To protect the
economic value that you've gone so and
worked so hard for. And so I see this
across the economy, right? If you go and
you look, what is a huge part of the
economy right now? It's AI. And the more
that we build out data centers and power
generation and all these different
things, that is leading to job creation,
that's leading to more investments,
that's leading to all these benefits in
the US economy. Okay.
You know what I love about your channel
is you talk about Bitcoin will always go
up because governments will not stop
printing.
>> got no top cuz the dollar's got no
bottom. I love that. And that could be I
know he has to go. That could be a great
ending. Sounds good, guys. Thanks so
much for having me. Thank you, Anthony.
Take care.